Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials OS
New York University Archives
- Series I: Washington Square Area and Buildings, 222757
  - Subseries A: Buildings, 222796
    - University Prep School, Proposed New Building for (Mercer Street and West 4th Street): Architectural Plans, 1965-1966; 222817 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Warren Weaver Hall: plans, 1962-1963; 222816 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Washington Place East Building (18-24 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, faculty club, 1963, undated; 222815 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Washington Square Aerial Photos: Photo Bureau Prints (2), 1971; 222814 (Box 1)
    - Washington Square Arch: Artist's rendering by William Fisher, undated; 232088 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Washington Square Center Area/Block Property Maps, 1939, undated; 222813 (Box 13)
    - Washington Square Center Map, September 1967; 222811 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Washington Square Center (School of Education Students Building and South Building): Architectural Plans, undated; 222810 (Box 13)
    - Washington Square East: Building Images, undated; 222809 (Box 1)
    - Washington Square Park aerial photograph (by Fairchild Aerial Surveys), circa 1930s to 1950s; 222808 (Box 20)
    - Washington Square Center Campus/Park: site maps for buildings, future buildings, development. Maps of existing property use, area analysis, rejected planning proposals to zoning commission, 1954-1970 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Washington Square Arch preliminary drawings (?) by E. Marugg, undated (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    - Washington Square Park: Aerial View (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated; 222807 (Flat-file 2, Drawer 14)
    - Washington Square Park plans: Traffic Restricted to Local Needs Only, proposed by The Washington Square Association (5 copies), May 1958 (Box 20)
    - Washington Square Park: Maps, plans, changes, sketches, 1958-1959; 222806 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Washington Square Park and surrounding buildings, showing construction of Bobst Library (aerial photograph), circa 1969-1973 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - Washington Square Park: Plans for Commencement, 1987; 222805 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Washington Square Park: Renovation Plans (copies), 1939; 222804 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Washington Square Park: Traffic Study, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Washington Square Park: Topographical Survey, 1981; 222803 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Washington Square Park and surrounding campus buildings, 3-D building sketches on block layout maps (2 folders), circa 1973-2017 (Flat-file-folder 1 Right, Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
    - Washington Square South: Artist Renderings, undated; 222802 (Box 38)
    - Washington Square Southeast: Proposal of New York University Relating to Washington Square Southeast Project, January 1960; 222801 (Box 38)
    - Washington Square North and Fifth Avenue block building plan: "Sketch of Rhine Lander(sp?) property showing in dotted lines proposed new building as of January 1950" (Box 20)
    - Washington Square North buildings, looking north (map/plans), undated (Box 20)
    - Washington Square Village: typical apartment floor plans, circa 1957-1967; 222800 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Waverly Building: architectural drawings, 1969-1974; 222799 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans (4 folders), 1960-1965 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans, 1961-1962; 222798 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans, 1961, 1963 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 15)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans, 1961-1965 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 15)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans, 1963-1964 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 12)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): plans, 1999 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 12)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): Artist renderings, interior and exterior space sketches and paintings of exterior (2 folders of paintings/sketches), 1960; 222892 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): HVAC, engineering plans, 1961-2000 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Washington Square South Site renderings, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Admissions building: sketches of signs, exterior view of entrance, 1963 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East): plans/schematics, 2001 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Rubin Residence Hall: plans for plumbing, 1969-1970 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Washington Square Mews: Ireland House: proposal plan presentation boards, undated (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 1 Fifth Avenue: floor plans, undated (Box 23)
    - Schwartz Plaza blueprints/plans, 1995 (Flat-file-folder 2)
      Transferred by the Office of the Provost, 2017. The accession number associated with this transfer is 2017.012
    - Washington Square East area: Philip Johnson model (photograph) of unrealized plan for atrium between Bobst/Stern, circa 1973-1980s (Drawer 11)
    - Washington Square East Atrium: Philip Johnson sketches of unrealized arched glass atrium between Bobst and Stern, circa 1973-1980s (Drawer 11)
    - 53 Washington Square South, King Juan Carlos I of Spain Center: blueprints/floorplans, 1995 (Box 31)
    - Unidentified buildings: architectural renderings, exterior and interiors (3 sketches/paintings), 1987, 1994, undated (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Unidentified Building: Board Mounted architectural drawing, undated; 244705 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
    - Unidentified building: artists rendering of exterior by Randolph Assoc., undated (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Unidentified Building: Charcoal/Watercolor, undated; 244704; Fisher, William (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
  - Subseries B: Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, 222758
    - Bobst Library Development Plans Book, circa 1950s-1960s; 222795 (Box 12)
    - Plans: Main Floor, Subcellar, Level B, 11th floor; sign for floors and corresponding call numbers/collections; Proposed Site Plan (1966); floor area calculations, 1964-1973 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Schedule of Drawings presented by Johnson and Foster to Dormitory Authority of the State of New York, 1969 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Exterior: Artist Renderings (2 folders), circa 1950s-1960s; 222794 (Box 38)
    - Interiors: Artist Renderings (4 pieces), undated, 1966; 222792 (Flat-file-folder 1 Right)
    - First Annual Bobst Literary Award Banquet: Front Elevation, circa 1983; 222790 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - First Annual Bobst Literary Award Banquet: Main Floor Plan, 1983 October 26; 222789 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Floor Plans, 1974; 222788 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Frontal and Sectional Views, 1967; 222787 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 18)
    - Master compilation plans for: main, mezzanine, typical floor, cellars/subcellars, etc., January 11, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Early Library Plans, March 22, 1965; 247149 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Master Plans Compilations (Johnson and Foster), 1969; 222785 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Master Plans Compilation, 1973; 222786 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Philip Johnson Plan Compilations, 1973-1974; 222784 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Photograph: Interior with students at table in room, undated; 222783 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Site Studies, Zoning plans, 1964-1966; 222782 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Site plan of zoning lot for proposed library, January 5, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unspecified/typical Floor plans, 1969; 222781 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Alpine Sheet Metal Drawings, 1968; 222791 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - A Level (Subcellar), 1966-1970; 222780 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - A Level (Subcellar), Renovations, 1979; 222779 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - B Level (Cellar), undated; 222778 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Level B: Furniture design for Cataloging and Acquisitions Department: floor plans, 1995 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Exterior stone details, reflected ceiling plan for various levels, lighting fixtures, stairs, etc.: plans, 1966 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - First Floor, Miscellaneous Roof Details, Cellar/subcellar, North-South Section,directional elevations, various floor plans, roof, site plan and zoning information, etc., 1966-1968 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - First Floor: plans, 1967, 1971; 222777 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Mezzanine: plans, 1965-1967; 222776 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - 2nd Floor: Avery Fisher Music and Media Center space layout and floor plans, 1985; 222774 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 3rd-12th Floor (12th Floor Furniture Layout, President's Office) plans: 2 folders, 1966-1973; 222773 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Bobcat Layout, 1983 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Book Conveyor and Pneumatic Tube Systems, 1968-1969; 222772 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Bookstacks, 1963-1970; 222771 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Card Catalogs, 1971-1972; 222770 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Carrels, 1971-1972; 222769 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Duct, Electrical, Lighting, and Telephone Systems, 1967-1979; 222768 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Faculty Study Areas, 1966; 222767 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - First Floor Control Counters, 1968; 222766 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Lounges floor layout, shelvingsketches, 1969; 222765 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Mail Room and Shipping, undated; 222764 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 19)
    - Multi-Media Center floor plans, 1971; 222763 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Reserve Reading Room (Floor not specified) plans, 1970; 222762 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Roof Plan, undated; 222761 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 19)
    - Staff Work Areas: plans, 1965-1970; 222760 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Stern School of Business Graduate Library Design Development Plans Set, 1991 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Tables, 1971; 222759 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 20)
    - Tisch Hall Plaza Monument, Founders Memorial Monument: rubbing of monument plaque, architectural plans, 1973 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Turnstyle and information desk, 1998 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 20)
    - Unknown artist painted sketches of room interiors, class rooms, meeting rooms, floor interior sketches, undated (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    - Early exterior sketch (is this Bobst?), circa 1960s (Drawer 11)
    - Very early sketch of interior, Lobby area (mounted on long panel), circa 1960s (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Very early sketch of interior, lower level area (mounted on long panel), circa 1960s (Flat-file-folder 1)
- Series II: University Heights Area and Buildings, 222698
  - Subseries A: Buildings, 222712
    - University Heights Campus, East 25th Street: Aerial Photos, circa 1900s; 222756 (Box 1)
    - Campus: Map and Aerial Photograph, 1937, 1939; 222755 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Central Campus Overview (illustrating location of new buildings): artist renderings, color paintings, undated; 222754 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Marcel Breuer Building Views: Artist Renderings, undated; 222737 (Flat-file 2, Drawer 12)
    - Marcel Breuer Comprehensive campus plan Section I, 1963; 222736 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Marcel Breuer Comprehensive campus plan Section II, 1963; 222735 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Altschul House: floor plans, 1964; 222722 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Alumni Gymnasium: architectural plans, 1926, 1931, 1964; 222752 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Anderson Avenue Proposed Dormitory: zoning study, February 28, 1966; 222718 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Begrisch Hall: floor plans, drawing of building sign/plaque, 1965; 222721 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Bliss Building: architectural plans, 1936, 1964; 222751 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Butler Hall: floor plans, 1964; 222720 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Dormitory: floor plans/layouts, June 5, 1965; 222719 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Engineering/R.O.T.C. Building: proposal, plans, 1940-1941 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Faculty Club: architectural plans, 1962, 1964; 222750 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Four-Building Complex, campus buildings, public spaces: artist renderings (3 color paintings), 1958; 222749 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Gould Hall, dormitory: plans (2 folders), 1948-1949, 1960-1964; 222879 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Gould Memorial Library (McKim, Mead and White, Architects) plans, 1896-1900; 222748 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Gould Memorial Library plans, 1947, 1956 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Gould Memorial Library: Alteration Plans, 1963-1969; 222747 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Gould Memorial Library: Alteration plans, 1964-1965 (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Gould Student Center: architectural plans, 1963; 222746 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Green Building: floor plans, 1964; 222717 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics: plans, 1948, circa 1961; 222745 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Hall of Fame: Blueprints, Aug 15, 1924; 222743 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 8)
    - Hall of Fame plans/blueprints, 1961, 1965, 1967; 222744 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, watercolor painting by Joseph Roberto, May 1964 (Box 13)
    - Havemeyer Laboratory and Annex: plans, exterior elevations, 1961, 1964; 222742 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Language Hall (McKim, Mead, and White, Architects) plans, 1894, 1947, 1965; 222741 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 1)
    - Loew Dormitory: architectural plans, sign/plaque drawings, 1955, 1964; 222740 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Loring Place, 1968, 1970; 222739 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - MacCracken Hall: architectural plans, 1964; 222738 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Mechanical and Engineering Design Lab: ground floor plan, 1964; 222716 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Natural Science Hall: architectural plans, 1899; 222734 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Nichols Chemistry Building, 1926, 1964-1965; 222733 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Old Engineering Building/Plant Office: floor plans, 1964; 222715 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - O.R.C. Armory: architectural plans, 1952-1953; 222753 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Philosophy Hall: architectural plans, 1948, 1963-1964; 222732 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Plaza Near Gould Library: Artist Renderings, undated; 222731 (Flat-file 2, Drawer 12)
    - Religious Center: architectural plans, 1960; 222730 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Residence Hall, 1958; 222729 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Sage Engineering Building and Annex: architectural plans, 1961, 1964; 222728 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Science Library: architectural plans, 1961-1962; 222727 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Sedgewick Avenue Dormitory: sketches of floor plans, 1965; 222726 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - South Hall: architectural plans, 1949, 1964; 222725 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Technology II Engineering Building: photograph, circa 1950s-1960s; 222724 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Technology Building II: architectural plans, proposals for design (2 folders), 1963-1968; 222723 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - University Heights Library plans, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - West Hall: floor plans, 1964; 222714 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Watercolor Sketch of Campus, 1960s; 222713 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Campus: plans (plan of Fiske Kimball, consulting with McKim, Mead & White), August 25, 1924 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Campus: site development plan (Eggars & Higgins), September 10, 1952 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Development and Planning, 222699
    - University Heights North maps/surveys of campus: by George Hollerith, blueprints of proposed University College Grounds, block/buildings, layouts, etc., April 7, 1894, 1930-1961 (Box 13)
    - University Heights Dormitory Plans Book (Marcel Breuer and Associates Architects), January 1958; 222710 (Box 15)
    - University Heights Development Plans Book (Marcel Breuer and Associates Architects)-2 copies, 1963; 222711 (Box 11)
    - University Heights Tech II Building PIlot Scheme Book (Marcel Breuer Architects), 1963 (Box 11)
    - Campus Maps and Plans, Property Maps, Block maps re: expansion of campus, 1897, undated; 222708 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Campus: large-scale maps: Topographical, Blocks/building locations, etc., 1854-1972; 222701 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Main Campus: Projected Master Plans and Surveys of property, 1952, 1965-1966; 222702 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - University Heights Uptown Campus Landscaping Plans (blueprints, sketches), 1963, 1966; 222703 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - University Heights Area Long-Range Development Plan, 1963; 227191 (Box 11)
      Removed from the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4)
    - Blueprints, Aug 15, 1924; 222709 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 8)
    - Entrances (new entrance gate), Parking lots, Roadways around Hall of Fame terrace area: plans, 1960-1968; 222707 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Group Living Plan II: plans, 1962; 222704 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Sketch for Location of Apartment Houses: map, landscape plan (by Olmstead Brothers Landscape), 1919; 222700 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unknown building: plan by Professor Trowbridge for span, 1911 (Flat-file-folder 1)
- Series III: Other University Buildings, 222685
  - 1071 6th Avenue (at 41st Street): floor layouts/plans (2). Building seems to be arts-related, undated; 222697 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - NYU at University Valley-Sterling Forest, NY: apartment area survey, maps/sketches of surrounding area, plans for Commons Hall, Administration Building, Housing, etc., 1963-1964; 222696 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Bellevue Medical Center: Blueprints and Plans, circa 1956-1962; 222695 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Institute of Fine Arts (Uptown Manhattan, New York, NY): floor space survey, blueprints/floor plans, 1958, 1978; 222694 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Institute of Fine Arts (Uptown Manhattan, New York, NY): structural rehabilitation proposals from various companies, 1990 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Institute of Fine Arts photograph, circa 1980s; 222693 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Medical Center: allocation plans and future buildings added, November 12, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center (550 First Avenue): plans, 1962-1975 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Medical Center: Artist Renderings of Leidesdorf Plaza and front of building, front entrance area, 1968, 1971; 222692 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Medical-Dental Center: Institute of Oral Hygiene (East River and 20th Street, New York, NY): proposed building/floor plan sketches, 1937; 222689 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Medical-Dental Center: Carnegie Building, Dental School (East River and 20th Street, New York, NY): floor plans, 1964; 222691 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Medical-Dental Center: plans, 1964-1973; 222690 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Medical-Dental Center: plans, 1971 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - NYU Medical Center and Vicinity map, 1956; 227503 (Flat-file-folder 1 Right, Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 2)
  - Riverside Highrises: Artist Renderings, January 16, 1967; 222688 (Box 38)
  - Wall Street Center: Merrill Hall, Graduate School of Business Administration (100 Trinity Place): sign sketches, building plans, 1971; 222687 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Wall Street Center: Nichols Hall, Graduate School of Business Administration (90 Trinity Place): sketches of sign and floor plans, 1957; 222686 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Unknown building: artists/architect's color rendering of exterior, undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Alumni Hall (33 Third Avenue): plans for furniture layout, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 5)
- Series IV: Certificates, Diplomas, and Proclamations, 222597
  - Subseries A: Awards and Certificates, 222648
    - Blank certificates: Service Citation for 25 years or more (10 copies), undated; 222684 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificates: Certificate of Cooperation in Marshall Plan, December 29, 1951; 222682 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificates: College of Engineering Pre-Meteorology, undated; 222680 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificates: Hall of Fame, undated; 222679 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificates: Seminar for Executives in U.S. Securities Markets, undated; 222678 (Box 23)
    - Unsigned Certificates: Charles Waldo Haskins Association (13 certificates), undated; 222681 (Box 23)
    - Blank certificate: Graduate School of Business, completion of The School of Investment Company Management, 1966; 222647 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificate: School of Engineering completion certificate for Design Course for Project SETE, 1967; 222639 (Box 23)
    - Blank Certificate: Certificate of Achievement, Department of Journalism and Mass Communication, circa 1990s (Box 23)
    - Blank: paper embossed with University Heights Campus building, undated; 222656 (Box 23)
    - Blank: Founder's Day Award/Certificates. Nine variations of certificates, undated; 222667 (Box 14)
    - Certificate of Recognition for serving as alumni member of Board of Trustees or Governing Council, undated; 222677 (Box 23)
    - American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business certificate for completion of Workshop in International Business, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Award Certificate for NYU and Station WCBS-TV Program, "Long Before Shakespeare", 1962; 222674 (Box 23)
    - Brown, Elmer E. certificate for appointment to U.S. Commissioner of Education, by Theodore Roosevelt, June 23, 1906; 222673 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Certificate from U.S. Department of Defense in Honor of NYU Goliards, 1962; 222672 (Box 14)
    - Chase, Harry Woodburn. Appointment to member of Mayor's Business Advisory Committee, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Chase: Harry Woodburne. Appointment to Mayor's Committee of New York City's Golden Jubilee, 1948; 222675 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Citations (2): Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1959, 1965; 222671 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1917: American Field Service in France Certificate (donated ambulance), 1918; 222676 (Box 23)
    - Class of 1917 Presidential Citation, entered on the Roster of Honor, 1959; 222655 (Box 23)
    - Collins, G. Rowland: award of distinction for 25 years serving NYU, dedication Violet announcement from students of School of Commerce, and retirement proclamation, 1951-1952, 1959; 222670 (Box 16, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Eta Mu Phi: Charters (2), 1922, 1939; 222668 (Box 14)
    - Pi Lambda Theta, Rho Chapter: Charter, May 31, 1924 (Box 14)
    - Delta Zeta Sorority Affirmation, 1941; 222669 (Box 14)
    - Greetings from Metropolitan and Westchester Chapters of the NY State Society of Professional Engineers to NYU College of Engineering, 1955; 222666 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Greetings to Other Universities: Blank, Tufts University, and Catholic University, 1939, 1976, undated; 222664 (Box 23)
    - J. Hester congratulations for his inauguration as President of New York University, circa 1962; 222665 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Scroll of Honor to NYU from Histadruth Ivrit of America, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Education by Radio and Television: Award to Radio Department for "The Dream that Grew", 1954; 222661 (Box 23)
    - Mayoral Proclamation of NYU Week, October 13-20, 1981; 222660 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mayoral Proclamation of NYU Kick off "Celebration 2000" year-long celebration of millennium, October 8, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - NYU Millennium Time Capsule contents list, October 8, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - NYU College Prize Certificate (8 copies to different high schools), 1893; 222658 (Box 14)
    - Men in Finance Award, March 31, 1959; 222659 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Oliva, L. Jay. Proclamation honoring him on NYU Presidency, from Council of City of New York; and poster of Ireland House, 1991 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Sprague, Chaplain Ezra: Military Decoration, May 5, 1891; 222652 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Testimonial for Charles Butler LL.D. for 55 years of service to NYU and hand drawn maps of town blocks and Orleans County, 1846-1864, 1892; 222651 (Box 16, Folder 2, Flat-file 5, Drawer 13)
    - Violet Dedication, 1951; 222650 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 12)